Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009, bulk 1981-2009.
7616
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays
54.0 cubic ft.
correspondence, general subject files, videocassettes, audiocassettes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (P-FLAG) records consist of documents pertaining to the operations of the organization, including administrative records, project files, planning documents, regional directors' files, budget information, the 1992 Strategic Plan, correspondence, board meeting notes, by-laws and articles of incorporation, and other papers. Subject files include material on HIV/AIDS and HIV/AIDS care, family support networks, and other organizations and services in the field of gay rights and AIDS support. Also included are audiocassettes from P-FLAG National Conventions (1982-1996), and two videos.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (P-FLAG) was born when Jeanne Manford, a New York school teacher, expressed her outrage at her gay son's mistreatment by local police in a published letter to the New York Post in 1972. The public response to her statement, "I have a homosexual son, and I love him," was so great that she held the first support group meeting for parents of gay children in March 1973 at the Metropolitan Duane Methodist Church in Greenwich Village. By 1976, when the Los Angeles chapter was started by Adele Starr, numerous groups had formed around the country.
The first national meeting was held in 1979 to coincide with the first March on Washington for Gay Rights, and Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays was officially founded in 1981 with its headquarters in Denver, Colorado and was incorporated in 1982. In 1989, it moved to Washington, D.C. In the 1990s, it added "families" to the organizational name. In 1997, there were fifteen regions, each headed by a regional director, over four hundred affiliate chapters, and 70,000 individual members worldwide.
P-FLAG's three-part mission includes support, education, and advocacy. Its peer group meetings help what P-FLAGers call "new" parents through their often negative reactions to and distress about the news that a child is gay, lesbian, or bisexual. P-FLAG also offers support to individuals whose spouses, parents, or other family members have "come out" to them. Parents and other family members also benefit from and provide educational resources which aid in the process of acceptance. Publications, fact sheets, readings lists, cassettes, conferences, seminars, and speakers bureaus form the backbone of the educational arm of P-FLAG's mission.
Advocacy often entails applying educational campaigns to points of political leverage including voting blocks and public bodies. For example, many P-FLAG chapters have become highly involved in supporting anti-discrimination initiatives and in combating anti-gay ballot initiatives. P-FLAG chapters also often march in local and national gay pride parades. On the national level, P-FLAG organized a multimedia public education program called "Project Open Mind." P-FLAG's national president Nancy McDonald joined other activists in a meeting with President Bill Clinton to urge him to support programs for gay youth and the Employment Non-Discrimination Act designed to ban anti-gay bias in the workplace. P-FLAG collaborates with the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force and the Human Rights Campaign to push a common agenda.
McDonald credits Executive Director Sandra Gillis with the surge of membership from 1993 to 1997. In this time, the number of affiliate chapters almost doubled.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Series I contains files related to P-FLAG's administration, including the Board of Directors, Regional Directors, affiliates and chapters. Includes materials related to development, finances, strategic planning, personnel, and membership, as well as the daily operations of the P-FLAG offices. Information regarding the "organizational grievance" of 1996-1997 is also included. Also, oversize meeting diagrams.
Series II includes the correspondence of various P-FLAG officials, as well as some correspondence related to specific P-FLAG projects, for example the Respect All Youth (RAY) Project.
Series III contains general subject files including (among others): P-FLAG Directories; the Public Services Announcements Project; the Spouse Task Force and Straight Spouse Support Network; lesbian/gay/bisexual youth issues, including youth suicide; various advocacy projects and lobbying efforts, including the Defense of Marriage and Employment Non-Discrimination Acts, the "Parents, Schools, Values" congressional hearings, materials for the Campaign for Military Services project, and testimony regarding discrimination of gays by the Boy Scouts of America.
Series IV contains files pertaining to the AIDS crisis, including correspondence and subject files. Series V pertains to the Family AIDS Support Project, including administrative information, correspondence, and general subject files.
Series VI contains P-FLAG publications, including draft and final versions, as well as media advertisements. Also, some annotated reprints distributed by P-FLAG. Some P-FLAG chapter publications are also included, including chapter newsletters.
Series VII pertains to Project Open Mind, a media campaign aimed at raising awareness about violence towards gays and lesbians. Includes the POM Campaign Manual, information about POM consultants, advertising (including TV buys), endorsements, fundraising, financial information, strategic planning, the POM Presentation Handbook, and POM training in Atlanta, Houston, St. Paul/Minneapolis, Seattle, and Tulsa.
Series VIII includes documentation pertaining to P-FLAG National Conventions: national guidelines, correspondence, registration, organizing/planning of convention, program/workshops, convention weekend materials, and publicity. Also includes materials related to P-FLAG regional conferences, as well as P-FLAG Leadership Training Institutes, which took place in association with the national conventions beginning in 1993.
Series IX consists of audiocassettes from P-FLAG National Conventions, as well as other tapes produced by P-FLAG. The numbering system was established by P-FLAG (except for tr7676a, a non-professional recording from the 1993 Convention in New Orleans). Tapes identified as "missing" were not received from P-FLAG. Occassional lacunae in the numbering system are identified: "Tape X does not exist."
Series X consists of news clippings, photocopied articles, and press releases about P-FLAG, gays and lesbians, family of gays and lesbians, etc.
Series XI consists of photographs of conferences, programs, PFLAGpole publications, scholarships, etc.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays.
Subjects:
Gays--Laws and legislation.; Parents of gays--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Correspondence in box 28 has been RESTRICTED UNTIL 2063.
Correspondence in box 48 has been RESTRICTED UNTIL 2056.
Box 59 is restricted to permission of the organization.
RELATED MATERIAL
Publications removed from collection 7616 and cataloged as individual books and serials in the Human Sexuality Collection are listed at the end of this guide under Separated Material.
SERIES LIST
Series I. P-FLAG Administration
Boxes 1, 2, 6, 17, 21, 23-27, 41-42, 49-53, 59, 63
Foundation of the organization (articles of incorporation, charters, revisions of by-laws, constitution and revisions, etc.)
Affiliates
Annual Reports
Board of Directors
Chapter Information
Finances and Fundraising
Regional Directors
Strategic Plan
State Councils
Directories
P-FLAG Organizational Grievance
Snapshot of Excellence Program
Series II. Correspondence
Boxes 2, 3, 6, 28-29, 42, 48-49, 53, 56-57
Series III. General Subject Files
Boxes 3, 7, 18, 29-36, 42-43, 49, 54-56, 63
Public Service Announcements Project
Straight Spouses Network/Task Force Information
Respect All Youth Project
Campaign for Military Service Project
Pledge Project
State Organizing
Series IV. AIDS
Boxes 3, 4, 36, 43
Correspondence
Series V. Family AIDS Support Project
Boxes 4, 5, 36-37, 55
Series VI. Publications
Boxes 5, 7, 17, 22, 37-38, 43-46, 49, 55, 58, 64
P-FLAG Advertisements
Chapter Newsletters
Series VII. Project Open Mind
Box 19, 38, 46, 49, 55, 57
POM Strategic Planning
POM Trainings On Site
Series VIII. Conferences
Boxes 17, 20, 38-39, 46, 49
P-FLAG National Conventions
P-FLAG Regional Conferences
Series IX. Audiocassettes and Videocassettes
Boxes 8-16
Series X. Media
Boxes 39-40, 47, 60-63
Series XI. Photographs
Boxes 69-70
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Administration
  - Foundation of the organization (articles of incorporation, charters, revisions of by-laws, constitution and revisions, etc.)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, Bylaws, 1993-1997 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Bylaws, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Organizational Documents, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Advertising, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Army Times Publishing Company, BLADE, Comprint, Non-Profit Times, Times Journal/Army Times Publishing Company
  - Organization History, 1979-1984 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    "Parents and Friends of Gays is proud to join the National March on Washington;" "Parents Groups Nationwide Establish Federation;" etc.
  - Organization History, 1987-1998 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    Speeches, Video Transcripts, etc.
  - Affiliates
    - Mailings, 1992, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Mailings 15 July - 23 March, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Mailings 6 June - 1 November, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Mailings 6 December - 8 March, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Mailings 31 May - 30 August, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Mailings 24 October - 2 February, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Mailings March - 9 May, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Mailings 23 May - May, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Mailings Nov. 93-Winter 95, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Mailings, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Mailings, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Mailings, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Updates/Mailings, 11/94 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Updates/Mailings, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Updates/Mailings, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Affiliation revisions, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Mailings, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Mailings, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly mailing, 12/2000 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly mailing, 12/2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Mailings to affiliates, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - International Affiliates--Policy, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Certificates/Chapter Affiliates, 1994-1996 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Affiliate questionnaires--faith issues, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Paper Chapter Affiliation Documentation, ca.1998 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Affiliate Mailings, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Affiliation Packet Changes, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Affiliate Mailing, 6/15/00 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Affiliate Mailing, 9/5/00 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Affiliate Mailing, 12/6/00 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - American Express corporate card information, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting notice, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports
    - Printed annual reports, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports - 1989-1990, 1996, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Annual Report, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 51)
    - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 65, Folder 52)
    - Annual Report, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 53)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 54)
    - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 55)
    - Chapter Annual Reports, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      Metro DC July 2004-June 2005, PFLAG NH Report May 2005, PFLAG NH 2006 Annual Meeting, PFLAG Jersey Shore Annual REport - October 2006, Greater Boston Safe Schools and Communities Project 2004-2005, other Greater Boston PFLAG materials, Philadephia Summary of Activities, PFLAG Olympia Chapter Open Meeting Program History, Columbia/Howard County Annual Summary of Activities, PFLAG Keene Chapter Report 2005, Concord, NH Chapter 2005Annual Summary of Activities, Central Maryland PFLAG 2006, Fairbanks, Alaska 2005Annual Summary of Activities, Syracuse, NY 2005 Summary of Activities, Jackson, WY 2005 Annual Summary of Activities, Erie and Crawford Counties Annual Summary of Activities 2005
  - Board of Directors
    - Contact information, general, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Advance packet and minutes of meetings Anaheim, California, 10/1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Advance packet, reports, and minutes of meetings, Silver Spring, Maryland, 4/1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Advance packet, reports, and minutes of meetings, Charlotte, North Carolina, 10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Advance packet, reports, and minutes of meetings, Chevy Chase, Maryland, 4/1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Minutes and materials, meetings, Seattle, Washington, 9/1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Minutes and materials, meetings, Washington, D.C., 4/1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Minutes and materials, meetings, New Orleans, Louisiana, 9/1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Minutes and materials, meetings, Itasca, Illinois, 2/1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - By-Laws, 10/1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - By-Laws, 10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, memoranda, statements, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors misc., 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Board Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Mailings, 21 September - 18 February, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Mailings, 4 March - 13 May, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Mailings, 6 June - 12 August, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Mailings, 25 August - 8 March, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Mailings, 23 March - 18 December, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Mailings, 2 February - 18 April, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Mailings, 23 September - December, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Mailings, 4 February - 9 January, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Mailing Checklists, 23-26 September, Chicago, IL, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Mailing Checklists, 13-16 May, Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Budget/workplan; finance/audit; reports/amendments; other policies; governance policies; by-laws; includes miscellaneous items inserted in front and back pockets of binder, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
    - Board of Directors' Resource Manual, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
    - Board skills building, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Misc. materials, pre-1990(?) (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Board communication, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Board committees, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Biographies, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Meeting materials, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Board meeting materials- Seattle, 9/92 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Board meeting materials, 1/92 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Board structure, strategic plan, board meeting minutes, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Board meeting materials, 10/92 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Board protocols (mailings), 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Board fundraising, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Mitzi Henderson Bio, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Board, regional director, and strategic plan meeting materials, 4/1993 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Board meeting materials, 9/1993 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Board meeting materials, 12/1993 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Misc. files, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Board nominations committee, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Board election materials, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Board of directors' bios, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Mailings, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Board of Directors Report, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Board and chapter mailings, Dec. 1990-Aug. 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 60-61)
    - Board and chapter mailings, Dec. 1990-Aug. 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Board and chapter mailings, Oct. 1991-July 1993, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 2-4)
    - Annual meeting, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Board misc., 1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Board retreat, 1/15/1990 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Strategic Plan, 9/1992 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Dallas Board meeting, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Misc. board/executive director materials, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors Resource Manual, 12/8/1995 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Board policy, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Oversize Meeting Diagrams (Mapcase-folder 1)
      From San Francisco meeting 1/1993: Excellence Survey, Leadership Training, Affiliate Development Committee, 2 misc. sets of of papers; 2 sets of misc. papers, [n.d.]
    - Board members, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Monthly office reports, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Seeking Spanish language contacts, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Marketing strategy proposal, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Steering committee on religious issues, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Executive Director report to Board of Directors/Regional Directors, 1993-1995 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors materials, 1993-1997 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors meetings, May, Sept. 1994 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - PFLAG membership survey--preliminary report, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Executive Director reports, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Related Organizations, 1994-2000 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Administrative misc., 1994-2004 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - General process info, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Policy Development Meeting, Apr 1995 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - PFLAG Board Training with John Carver, Feb. 1995 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Board of Directors meeting, May 1995 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - John Carver model, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Board of Directors memo, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Board of Directors meeting, May 11-12, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Aug 1996 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Governance policies, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Board of Directors materials, governance, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Governance, 1996-2000 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Board of Directors materials, 1996-2000 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Openness Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Administrative misc., 1997-2000 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Conflict of interest forms, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Janice Hughes, communications--packet for reporters, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Membership, Summer 1998 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Annual Board Meeting, Sept. 1998 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Nov. 1998 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Board Development and Functioning (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Board Orientation, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors materials governance, 1998-99 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Governance, 1998-2001 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Structure committee, 1998-2003 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--bio, press release, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--Administrative misc, 1998-2000 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--trips, 1998-2000 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--various contacts, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Jan. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Feb. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Mar. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Apr. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, May 2000 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, June 2000 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Jul. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Aug. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Sept. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Oct. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Dec. 2000 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Jan. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Feb. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Mar. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Apr. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, May 2001 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Jun. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Jul. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Aug. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Sept. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Kingdon, Kirsten--chronological file, Oct. 2001 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Beeman, Paul--speeches and articles, 1998-2000 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Beeman, Paul, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Board of Directors materials, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - PFLAG Training Report, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Car rental/hotel info, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Membership training, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Feminist Expo 2000--request declined, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Governance, 1999-2001 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Administrative misc., 1999-2002 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Policy governance model, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Kolodny, Debra--management workshops, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Staff retreat, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Board chronological file, Dec. 2000-Jan 2001 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Volunteer management, 2000-2004 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Board meeting, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Communication survey, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Administrative misc., 2001-2003 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - Weill, Debbie--PFLAG timesheet, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - Administrative materials, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - Policies and Procedures (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Leadership Training (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Membership, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 55)
    - Businesses near the national office, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - Office policies, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 57)
    - Weill, Debra (field and policy coordinator)--PFLAG info, position info, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 58)
    - Weill, Debbie--trips and travel, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Schlitter, Ron--chronological file, Oct. 2003 (Box 51, Folder 60)
    - Schlitter, Ron--chronological file, Feb. 2004 (Box 51, Folder 61)
    - Schlitter, Ron--chronological file, May 2004 (Box 51, Folder 62)
    - Schlitter, Ron--chronological file, Jul. 2004 (Box 51, Folder 63)
    - Time sheets, misc. forms, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Diversity training handouts (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Various meetings, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Media training (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Weiner-Mahfuz, Lisa--writing samples (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Information
    - Chapter Building, 10/1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Materials re affiliation
    - Chapter Building, 7/1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Minutes and notes re establishing a National office, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Chapter Start-up Kit, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      a.k.a. "Packet A," used when someone wants to see what it means to start a chapter in their area